<players>
    <player>
        <name>Magnus Carlsen</name>
        <photo>carlsen.png</photo>
        <description>
            Magnus Carlsen is the current world chess champion. To many people, he’s the best to ever play the game, along with Garry Kasparov and Bobby Fischer.
            Carlsen had an aggressive style of play as a youth, not afraid to offer material for activity. 
            As he matured, Carlsen found that this risky playing style was not as well suited against the elite of the chess world. 
            Slowly Carlsen's style became more universal, capable of handling all sorts of positions well.
            Carlsen's endgame prowess has been described as among the greatest in history
        </description>
        <favorite-openings>
            <opening played="70">
                Ruy López Opening
            </opening>
            <opening played="55">
                Queen's Gambit Declined
            </opening>
            <opening played="23">
                Indian Game
            </opening>
        </favorite-openings>
    </player>

    <player>
        <name>Daniil Dubov</name>
        <photo>dubov.png</photo>
        <description>
            Daniil Dubov is a Russian grandmaster and world-class player.
            Dubov's style is very aggressive and creative, and he shows fantastic attacking abilities in his best games.
            His creativity on the board often surprises other Grandmasters, and it's one of the reasons he was able to defeat Magnus Carlsen on several occasions.
        </description>
        <favorite-openings>
            <opening played="36">
                Queen's Gambit Declined
            </opening>
            <opening played="30">
                Sicilian Defense
            </opening>
            <opening played="23">
                King's Indian Attack
            </opening>
            <opening played="20">
                English Opening
            </opening>
        </favorite-openings>
    </player>

    <player>
        <name>Bobby Fischer</name>
        <photo>fischer.png</photo>
        <description>
            Bobby Fischer is an American-born chess master who became the youngest grandmaster in history when he received the title in 1958.
            His youthful intemperance and brilliant playing drew the attention of the American public to the game of chess, particularly when he won the world championship in 1972.
            His victories commonly resulted from surprise attacks or counterattacks rather than from the accumulation of small advantages, yet his play remained positionally sound.
        </description>
        <favorite-openings>
            <opening played="30">
                Sicilian Defense
            </opening>
            <opening played="22">
                King's Indian
            </opening>
            <opening played="18">
                Caro Kann
            </opening>
        </favorite-openings>
    </player>
</players>